calexotics.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy

### Overview

Our users’ privacy is very important to us. Below we describe information that we may receive in connection with your use of the Services (as defined in our Terms of Use), how and why we receive it, and the steps we take to protect your privacy.

By using the Services, you are consenting to the manner in which CalExotics (as defined in our Terms of Use) will receive, use, disclose and otherwise manage your information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Additionally, when you provide information to CalExotics, you agree that the information is true, accurate, current, and complete.

### Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes CalExotics' treatment of certain information obtained or disclosed by CalExotics, including information we obtain when you use Services or share information with any of CalExotics’ third party partners. Carefully review this policy and contact us if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CalExotics does not own or control, or to individuals whom CalExotics does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties from which CalExotics may obtain or to which CalExotics may disclose user information as set forth in this Policy. The practices of such third parties are governed by their respective applicable privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

### Policy Changes

This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy or our information practices change in the future, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on the Site. Your continued use of the Services following any changes to this policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

### Information We Receive About You

We receive information about you when you visit and/or use our Services, including certain personal information about you and certain non-personal information about you. In some cases, we may request that you provide some of the information identified below to obtain access to certain services that we provide. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to access these Services. Our affiliates and other third parties also receive certain information about you when you when you use or access the Services, including the information described below.

We receive certain information about you when you visit and/or use our Services, including personal information, which is information that can be used to personally identify you. This information may be obtained directly by CalExotics or through any of its third party partners, and includes but is not limited to your first name, last name, birthdate, gender, billing address(es), shipping address(es), e-mail address(es), telephone number(s), payment information (including but not limited to credit card, debit card, gift card, rewards program, or coupon code information), location information (including but not limited to continent, providers, country, region, zip code, city, store vicinity, and others), order and purchase history, search queries, product and service preferences, account preferences, status, and information (including but not limited to username(s), password(s), and settings, and others), social media contact information, contact lists, and other information relating to your use of the Services.

We may also automatically collect certain non-personal information about your visit to the Services, including the device(s) you use to access our Services. Non-personal information is data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with you, and includes but is not limited to technical information about how you access the Services, including but not limited to browser information, operating system, device information, unique device identifiers, IP address, referring site/application, visit metrics, action metrics, page view metrics, search metrics, and others.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, aggregated personal information that is made anonymous is considered non-personal information. If we do combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for so long as it remains combined.

### How We Use the Information We Receive About You

We use and store the information that we receive about you, including your personal information, as necessary to conduct our business and to provide you and other users with the best possible products and services. As some examples, we use and store your information to fulfill orders, to provide you with suggestions and information in which you may be interested (including but not limited to offers related to your purchases through the Services), to measure or understand effectiveness of advertisements you and others see (including but not limited to serving you targeted advertisements), to protect the integrity and operation of the Services, and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research and service improvement. Should you place an order on our website, we also reserve the right to contact you at a later date to inform you of promotions and other special offers. You can opt out of these offers at any time.

To conduct our business and to best serve you, we may share or provide access to your information, including your personal information, with certain third parties, including but not limited to service providers that provide support services to us or that help us market our products and services. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with third parties (other than our affiliates and related entities) unless we have received your permission, given you notice (such as telling you about it in this Privacy Policy), or removed your name and any other personally identifying information from it.

We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose, including but not limited to providing it to third parties for marketing, advertising, analytics, or other uses.

We may also, in certain instances, disclose your information, including your personal information, when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, or bring legal action to protect your safety or rights or the safety or rights of CalExotics or others. We may also disclose your information, including your personal information, when you ask us to do so or when we believe it is required by law or as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

If CalExotics is sold to or merges with another company, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets, subject only to agreement by the acquirer that the information will be subject to the same or substantially similar privacy protections as those established by this Privacy Policy, and without any requirement of a consumer privacy ombudsman. This may include personal information.

We store your information for as long as is necessary to conduct our business and to provide the best possible products and services to you, including for the uses described above.

### How We Protect Your Information

Protecting your information is very important to us. However, unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us. You agree that CalExotics and our affiliates will have no liability for disclosure of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

### Making Purchases

When you place an order with CalExotics, we ask you to provide certain information, depending on the nature of the Services; including, Payment Method, Credit Card Account Number and Expiration Date (if applicable), Name (as it appears on credit card), "Bill To" Address (as it appears on your credit card statement), "Ship To" Address (if different from billing address), Daytime Phone Number, and your Email Address. This information is necessary to process your order.

By making a purchase via the Services, you consent to our providing your information, including your personal information, to third parties as is necessary to process the requested transaction, including but not limited to credit card processors and banks.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Cookies are data files saved to your computer's hard drive when you visit a site. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available.

We may use session and persistent cookies, either directly or through a third party partner, as well as along other tracking technologies (including but not limited to pixel tags and web beacons) to collect information about you in order to conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible services and products. If you turn cookies off (and we use this feature), you won't have access to many features that make your Site experience more efficient and some of the Services will not function properly. We may also use cookies and other tracking technologies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests.

### Disclosures to Third Parties

CalExotics relies on third-party vendors and service providers to provide support and assistance for our Services and products. We may share your personal information with such third parties to help us conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products and services. We may contract with various third-party service providers, including but not limited to payment processors, website hosting partners, and others. We may also work with third party advertising, marketing and analytics partners to serve ads on this or other sites, using information collected through the use of industry standard technologies such as cookies and pixel tags. These third parties may receive information about you over time and across different websites when you use the Services.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with third parties unless we have received your permission or given you notice (such as telling you about it in this Privacy Policy). We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose, including providing it to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### User Age Requirement ****

The Services are not directed to persons under the age of eighteen (18) years (or twenty-one (21) years in places where eighteen years is not the age of majority) Users must be at least age of eighteen (18) years (or twenty-one (21) years in places where eighteen years is not the age of majority) to access, use, or register for the Services. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from persons under the age of eighteen (18) years (or twenty-one (21) years in places where eighteen years is not the age of majority).  If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a user under the age of eighteen (18) years (or twenty-one (21) years in places where eighteen years is not the age of majority) we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

### Opting-out, Removing, or Modifying Your Information

We offer several ways for you to update your information that is obtained and stored by CalExotics, including options to change your account preferences, remove your email from e-mail updates, and others you may contact the Company by sending an email to optout@calexotics.com.
